Hey... Hello...
ちょっと... こんにちは...
I feel more like cleaning than peace...
平和より清掃感が...
It looks great.
見た目が上手いですね
Have you tried it?
してみました?
Maybe JC...
JCかも...
Junior high school student?
中学生?
Junior high school students...
中学生...
Should I take the test?
検定取るかな?
Sayla never wears clothes?
セイラは服は着たことはない?
Not really.
ないですね
It's here.
ここですね
Local youth...
地方の青春な...
It's erotic, if you turn your stomach a little.
エロいですよね、ちょっとお腹をめくると
You can see it briefly.
チ ラッと見えますね
It's too cute.
可愛すぎますね
What do you think?
どうですか?
Last time you had sex, didn't you get pregnant?
前回仲出ししましたけど、妊娠しなかったですか?
I didn't.
しなかったです
I ended up putting out a lot though.
いっぱい出しちゃいましたけど
A huge amount...
すごい大量に...
It's your second time, so have you gotten used to it?
2回目だから慣れましたかね?
I'm used to it.
慣れました
Your legs are long, so try stretching them out a bit.
足が長いからちょっと伸ばしてみて
It's long.
長いね
Can I let it all out?
い っぱい出していいですかね?
You can also throw up Roden.
ローデンも吐いてもいいよ
Yes please.
はいにしよ
Okay.
いいよ
Noisy.
うるさいに
That's fine, not at all.
いいよ全然です
It's so cool.
ドスクールですね
Is it okay if I take a picture of the pump if it bothers me?
パンプ邪魔だったら撮っちゃっていいかな?
Is it okay if I take a picture if it gets in the way of the pump?
パ ンプ邪魔だったら撮っちゃっていいかな?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Is it okay?
いいっしょ?
Okay.
いいっしょ
I feel like it's really good.
マジでいい気がする
Show me as much as you can.
い っぱい見せて
Want to see something?
何か見てみる?
I don't look at it closely.
じっくり見ないからね
So spread it out and take a look.
じゃあ 広げて何か見てみて
It's packed, right?
詰まってるでしょ?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
This is Kuri-chan, right?
クリちゃんのこれでしょ?
Kuri-chan's.
クリちゃんの
amazing.
すごい
Can you put your finger in?
指入れないか?
Try putting your finger in.
指入れてみて
Can't you come in?
入れないか?
I can't enter.
入れない
Try putting it in a little bit.
ちょっと入れてみて
Are you putting it in?
入れてる?
Yeah.
うん
Everything goes.
すべていきます
No?
ダメ?
It's slippery.
すべったい
Did you do it?
すった?
Yeah.
うん
With revenge.
リベンジで
As strong as you like.
お好きな強さで
It's chewy.
もちいい
a little bit.
ちょっと
It's getting wet.
濡れてきましたね
I wonder if I can pull it out myself?
自分でちょっと抜き刺しできるかな?
Try it.
やって み て
Ah, I can't do it anymore.
あ、もうやんない
Let's try it.
やってみよう
You look happy.
う れしそうだね
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
I like phone calls, so keep it all the way in.
電話好きだから奥まで入れておいて
Try it.
やってみて
Ah, I can't do it anymore.
あ、もうやんない
You look happy.
うれしそうだね
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
I like phone calls, so keep it all the way in.
電話好きだから奥まで入れておいて
copper?
どう?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
copper?
どう?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Does it move?
動くの?
I love hearts.
心臓好きなんだ
I think I'll give it a try.
やってみようかな
amazing.
すごい
Don't hit your waist.
腰ぶっちゃうな
amazing.
すごい
Didn't it hurt?
痛くなかった?
Yeah.
うん
just with your mouth
口だけで
Sho.
しょ
It's just your mouth.
口 だけでしょ
Sho
しょ
What?
っぱ い?
Hey
おい
Is it?
しい?
delicious?
おい しい?
Nice?
いいな?
Yeah.
うん